http://www.actionwearinc.com/privacy-notice

My Cart
(0)
Total: $0.00
You have no items in your shopping cart.
PRIVACY POLICY
Actionwear Saskatoon Inc. is committed to protecting your privacy and security of your personal information. This policy discloses the privacy practices for Actionwear Saskatoon Inc. and its websites actionwear.ca and store.actionwear.ca. The statement does not include the privacy practices for partnered sites. We encourage our users who visit external sites from links within actionwear.ca and store.actionwear.ca to read the privacy statements of those sites, as their privacy practices may differ from ours and will govern their use of your information. If you have questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, please contact us via email at sales@actionwear.ca or by calling 1-866-933-3088 within Canada. If you prefer to write us our postal address is below.
Actionwear Saskatoon Inc.
114 Melville Street
Saskatoon, SK S7J OR1
How We Disclose Personal Data Actionwear Saskatoon Inc. will only disclose your Personal Data with your knowledge and as stated in this Privacy Policy or as indicated at the time of collection. This includes disclosures that will enable us to fulfill our obligations to you and allows us to manage our business operations. We will only share your Personal Data with third parties as is necessary to complete a transaction or provide a product, service, or feature that you have requested. We may disclose your Personal Data as described in this Privacy Policy and in the following ways:
To Affiliates, Partners, Vendors, and Suppliers These third parties, vendors, distributors, suppliers may have access to or process your Personal Data, but only to the extent it is necessary for them to
provide  products and services to us
provide you the products and services that you have requested. For example, we may use third-party providers to assist us with marketing and advertising our products and Services, delivering customer service and support
During Recruitment and Job Applications - When you apply for employment, we may collect your personal information, including any information contained on a resume or curriculum vitae.  We may keep the information you submit in connection with an application for employment or for future consideration.
To Enable the Use of Our Services - Personal Data that is collected through the Services may be used or disclosed to third parties in order to enable us to provide Services. For example, the actionwear.ca and or store.actionwear.ca websites may allow you to interface with a third-party website or application, such as Loomis or Fed Ex.
In Community Forums - Any information you post or disclose in our community forums, such as Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, or other sponsored pages on the Actionwear Blog is public. We cannot control the use of information disclosed in community forums, such as bulletin boards, blogs, chat rooms, and networking functions of mobile applications. Exercise caution when disclosing information in these public areas and be careful what Personal Data you disclose and how you disclose it. Content posted in our community forums, including advice and opinions, represents the views of the individuals who post that Content and such individuals bear sole and exclusive responsibility for the posting of that content. Actionwear Saskatoon Inc. does not necessarily endorse, support, verify, or agree with any content posted in our Community Forums.
As We Grow and Change – Corporate Transactions and Reorganizations - If Actionwear Saskatoon Inc. were to ever merge with another company, or if Actionwear were to decide to buy, sell, or reorganize some part or all of its business, we may disclose or transfer, to the extent permitted by law and in compliance with any applicable requirements to notify you, your Personal Data to prospective or actual purchasers or successor entities in connection with one of these transactions or reorganizations.
As Required by Law and Special Circumstances - We may be required, subject to applicable law, to disclose your Personal Data if: (i) it is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process: such as a court order, subpoena, search warrant, etc. or other legal requirements of any governmental authority, (ii) such a disclosure would potentially mitigate our liability in an actual or potential lawsuit, (iii) it is necessary to protect our legal rights or property, or (iv) it is necessary to protect the legal rights or property or physical security of others, or for the prevention or detection of crime and such disclosure is lawful.
Using Information We Collect
At Actionwear, we always want to provide you with the best possible shopping experience and fulfill your orders exactly as you've requested. In order to do this, we collect information that allows us to:
Process and track your order
Provide the services you request
Contact you about the status of an order
Send you catalogs or promotional offers we believe will be of interest to you
Identify your product and service preferences
Customize our communications to you
Improve our merchandise selection and customer service
Cookies
We regularly use technologies such as cookies. A "cookie" is a small file stored by your web browser on your computer. Cookies allow us to recognize who you are, when you arrive at our site, by associating an anonymous identification number in the cookie. At no time is your personally identifiable information stored within one of our cookies.
Cookies will be placed on your computer to collect non-personal information. The information that is collected through these cookies tells us things like which search engine referred you, how you navigated around our site, what you browsed and purchased. Understanding how you shop allows us to improve and personalize your shopping experience and speed your checkout process. Accepting cookies through your web browser is your personal choice. You can set your browser to disable cookies.
Actionwear Saskatoon Inc does not store your credit card information.
How We Use Email
When you provide us your email address, we may send you emails related to processing your order or to respond to a request. For example, after you place an order at actionwear.ca and or store.actionwear.ca, you will receive information via email to confirm your order, shipping notifications with tracking information and for billing purposes.
If you decide to participate, you may be sent email surveys to assist with improving our service to you our valued client.
Security
In our efforts to protect your information, Actionwear uses a variety of technical safeguards, such as firewalls, and we physically secure our servers.
The actionwear.ca and store.actionwear.ca websites contain links to other sites. Actionwear does not control the use of personally identifiable information on these websites. You should review the privacy policies of every website before providing any personal information. Actionwear is not responsible for the conduct or practices of any linked websites. These links are provided solely for the convenience and information of our visitors.
Privacy of Children on Our Website
Our website is not intended for use by children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.
Policy Changes
From time to time, we may use customer information for unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy policy notice. Before our information practices change, we will post these changes on our website. We encourage you to review our privacy policy periodically.
Questions or Comments?
If you have questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, please contact us via email at sales@actionwear.ca or by calling 1-866-933-3088 within Canada. If you prefer to write us our postal address is below.
Actionwear Saskatoon Inc.
1-866-933-3088 (Office) 1-306-934-2922 (Fax)
Actionwear is a Canadian owned and operated business that has been committed to manufacturing quality garments using trusted brands Since 1974.
Copyright © 2020 ActionWear. All rights reserved.
